<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Online RSA</title>
    <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/migrating2/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Online RSA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2007-{year} by 5 Star Online Training RTO #45332. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://onlinersa.com.au/migrating2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>All About the Online RSA Course | RSA FAQ</title>
      <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/About-the-Course.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/About-the-Course.html</guid>
      <description>How do I enrol?&#xD;You have two options to enrol.&#xD;First option: You can continue to enrol directly after the payment process by clicking the Start Now option on the page.&#xD;(you will not need to access your email) You will be taken to the student registration page, where you will need to click on&#xD;the &amp;quot;Begin Registration&amp;quot; button to setup your student account. You will then have to input your personal information&#xD;in the 6-step registration process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Wine Course | FREE with Your RSA Training</title>
      <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/Wine/Introduction-to-Wine.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/Wine/Introduction-to-Wine.html</guid>
      <description>(non accredited)&#xA;Understanding Wine Course Overview&#xD;If you&#39;re going to be serving alcohol you will probably be serving wine, so it may help your employment prospects if you know more about wine than just &amp;quot;it comes in two colours&amp;quot;. By completing this course you will be able to show potential employers in the restaurant or bar industry that you have some knowledge about wine and know how to have a conversation with customers to help them with purchases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online RSA Certificates | RSA FAQ</title>
      <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/RSA-Statements-of-Attainment.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/RSA-Statements-of-Attainment.html</guid>
      <description>How long do RSA statement of attainments last for?&#xD;It does vary between the States/Territories.&#xD;Victoria (VIC): Statements of attainment last for 3 years after which you must undertake a free refresher course.&#xD;There is a free online refresher course for people who would like to update their Victorian RSA training; please contact the Victorian Commission for Gambling and Liquor Regulation (VCGLR).&#xD;Western Australia (WA), South Australia (SA), Queensland (QLD) and Tasmania (TAS): require that you have successfully&#xD;completed the current nationally accredited course code for Provide Responsible Service of Alcohol SITHFAB021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online RSA Payment Options | RSA FAQ</title>
      <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/Payment-Options.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/Payment-Options.html</guid>
      <description>What are my payment options?&#xD;You have a choice between using PayPal or Credit card. If you would like to arrange a direct deposit, send a cheque or send a purchase order instead, please contact us to have this arranged.&#xD;How will this transaction appear on my credit card statement?&#xD;Purchases from this site will be listed on your statement as paid to eLearning Portal.&#xD;eLearning Portal/Enrolo are our payment processing and learning management system service providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State by State RSA Requirements Explained | RSA FAQ</title>
      <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/State-by-State-Requirements.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/State-by-State-Requirements.html</guid>
      <description>Can I get one RSA training course that will cover the whole of Australia?&#xD;Yes, but..&#xD;Unfortunately some states and territories have differing requirements for RSA training, assessment and certificate/badge/competency cards.&#xD;Therefore it is not possible to do one single course that will satisfy all requirements for all states, but, you are able to bridge your&#xD;qualification to the other states.&#xD;Our recommendation is that you should choose the state where you are most likely to start working and complete that course, making sure to&#xD;click on all of the available state variations when you come to the map sections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workplace Hygiene for Food Handlers Online</title>
      <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/Workplace-Hygiene/Workplace-Hygiene.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/Workplace-Hygiene/Workplace-Hygiene.html</guid>
      <description>(non accredited)&#xD;Overview&#xD;This course gives hospitality staff the necessary skills in food safety and food hygiene matters, ensuring compliance with the Australia New Zealand Food Standards Code Standard 3.2.2 Food Safety Practices and General Requirements.&#xD;This course is divided into the following four sections each with an online assessment;&#xD;Introduction&#xD;You and your workplace&#xD;Understanding contamination&#xD;Typical workplace tasks&#xD;Buy workplace hygiene on its own&#xD;$30 (includes GST)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Online RSA Technical Questions Answered | RSA FAQ</title>
      <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/Technical-Details.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/Technical-Details.html</guid>
      <description>I lost or forgot my Username/password - can I retrieve it?&#xD;You cannot retrieve your password, but you can reset it. Please return to the student login page and follow the instructions for a forgotten username or password.&#xD;Do I need to install any special software or apps?&#xD;No. Only a modern standards compliant web browser is required, eg. Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari, Microsoft Edge, etc..&#xD;Our preferred browsers to use are;&#xD;For desktop PC and Mac computers: Google Chrome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Questions About the RSA Answered | RSA FAQ</title>
      <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ.html</guid>
      <description>For answers to frequently asked questions please choose a category below and click a link for more details.&#xA;About the Course&#xD;How do I enrol?&#xD;Is it possible to fail the course?&#xD;Can people less than 18 years of age do the Online RSA training?&#xD;Do I need a Unique Student Identifier (USI)?&#xD;How long does it take to complete the course?&#xD;How do I reattempt Questions or Quizzes? How many times can I reattempt questions?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your RSA Training Provider Questions Answered | RSA FAQ</title>
      <link>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/Training-Provider.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://onlinersa.com.au/rsa/FAQ/Training-Provider.html</guid>
      <description>How can I ensure that a training provider is authorised to deliver the training?&#xD;5 Star Online Training Pty Ltd RTO #45332 is&#xD;registered in all states and territories to deliver Provide Responsible Service of Alcohol SITHFAB021 training&#xD;You can check whether an RTO is authorised to deliver the training by contacting your State/Territory liquor authority. There is a list of each State/Territory liquor&#xD;authority (along with contact details for each) here.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
